dealerrater.com 2019-12-27

# Car Dealer Reviews, Dealership Ratings, Cars For Sale - DealerRater.com

Last updated October 2019

DealerRater was founded in 2002 as the first car dealer review website worldwide. Our Site is part of the DealerRater network and is operated by DR Media Holdings, LLC ("DealerRater"). By using this Site, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to be bound by this Statement and agree to the DealerRater.com Terms of Use. 

We take your privacy seriously, and work to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read this Policy to learn more about how we protect your privacy before using this Site or submitting your personal information. By using this Site or submitting personal information, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information (as defined below) in accordance with the practices described herein. If you do not agree with these terms, do not use this Site or provide any personal information to us. 

What Information We Collect  
DealerRater collects personal information relevant to your use and the operation of the Site, including but not limited to your name, mailing address, phone number (including mobile phone number), e-mail address, geographic location as may be associated with a Submission or Dealer Review, and payment information (including credit card numbers) ("Personal Information"). We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our Site or use our applications, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, your IP address, your device identifiers, your Internet or wireless service provider, pages viewed or otherwise visited on the Site, and location-based information. 

How We Use Your Personal Information  
Personal Information and other collected information may be used to fulfill requests on your behalf, customize your experience, or provide you with information that may be of interest to you. DealerRater may also use your Personal Information to operate and facilitate your use of the Site, including but not limited to internal review, to improve the content of the Site, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site and applicable laws, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, deliver correspondence, communications, or services that you request, and to solicit your feedback. DealerRater does not store your payment information, and will only use it for processing. 

With Whom We Share Your Personal Information  
DealerRater will not sell your Personal Information to third parties. In an effort to display offers that may be of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Site. As a result of your use of the Site, such ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, IP address and clickstream information. DealerRater may engage third parties to help us provide the Site and manage our business, although these organizations are subject to confidentiality obligations and may only use your Personal Information for the purposes DealerRater defines. We may analyze your Personal Information and non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form which does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, advertisers, manufacturers, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

We may share, disclose, or provide your Personal Information to third parties: (i) when required to combat fraud or to protect our interests; (ii) to enforce the Privacy Policy or the applicable Terms of Use, Terms of Service, or API license grant; (iii) when required to do so by law or in response to legal process or lawful requests, including from law enforcement or government agencies; (iv) within and among our affiliates and subsidiaries; or (v) as part of a merger, sale of a business, sale of assets, or dissolution. 

We may use how you browse and shop in order to show you ads for DealerRater or our advertising partners that are more relevant to your interests. We may use cookies and other information to provide relevant interest-based advertising to you. Interest-based ads are ads presented to you based on your browsing behavior in order to provide you with ads more tailored to your interests. These interest-based ads may be presented to you while you are browsing our site or third-party sites not owned by DealerRater. 

We belong to ad networks that may use your browsing history across participating websites to show you interest-based advertisements on those websites. Currently, our Site does not recognize if your browser sends a “do not track” signal or similar mechanism to indicate you do not wish to be tracked or receive interest-based ads. You can opt-out of receiving interest-based ads from us by Contact Us and provide your full name and applicable account information, along with your request for opting out. Please note that if you choose to opt out, you will continue to see ads on our Site, but they will not be based on how you browse and shop. 

In addition to the sharing described elsewhere in this Policy, we will share personal information with companies, dealers, organizations or individuals outside of DealerRater when we have your consent to do so. 

Dealership Accounts  
Accounts belonging to dealerships may privately contact reviewers through our site on items related to a consumer review. When dealers make such contact, email addresses are not provided to either party without prior consent. DealerRater facilitates the interaction through the DealerRater platform. How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information You can generally access, review and update your Personal Information by logging in to your My Account page here and making the necessary changes. If you have any difficulty doing so or have other questions about the Personal Information we hold about you, please contact us at [support@dealerrater.com](mailto:support@dealerrater.com). To protect your privacy, we and our authorized employees and agents will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to or making corrections to your Personal Information. 

Cookies  
DealerRater uses "cookies" and other technologies to collect data that enables us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of the Site. Cookies are files sent to your browser and stored on your computer. If you do not want DealerRater to send cookies to your browser, you can set your browser options to reject cookies or notify you when a web site tries to put a cookie into your browser software. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some features of the Site. 

We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) to collect certain information relating to your use of the Site. Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the Site analyze how users use the site. You can find out more about how Google uses data when you visit our Site by visiting “How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps”, (located at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)). We may also use Google Analytics Advertising Features to provide you with interest-based advertising based on your online activity. For more information regarding Google Analytics please visit Google's website, and pages that describe Google Analytics, such as [www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). To learn more about interest-based advertisements and your opt-out rights and options, visit the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) and the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) websites ([www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)). Please note that if you choose to opt out, you will continue to see ads on our Site, but they will not be based on how you browse and shop. 

DealerRater gathers general information about visits to the Site. DealerRater uses this information to understand traffic on the Site, provide you with technical support, improve the Site, and provide the best online experience possible for our Users. 

How We Protect Your Personal Information  
We take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information in our custody or control from unauthorized access, use and disclosure, using security measures that are appropriate having regard to the sensitivity of the information. Our employees are trained and required to abide by our Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, however, due to the nature of the Internet it is impossible to guarantee the security of your information. 

Children's Privacy  
DealerRater is very concerned about protecting the privacy of children. DealerRater does not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years old or knowingly distribute such information. Children under 13 are not permitted to use the Site, and we request that children under 13 not submit any Personal Information to DealerRater. If a child under 13 has provided DealerRater with Personal Information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact DealerRater immediately Contact Us to delete this information from our files. 

External Links  
Where any links found on the Site link to pages not belonging to DealerRater, those external pages are not governed by this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you read the privacy statements posted on those other pages to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing Personal Information. 

Amendment to this Privacy Policy  
Please note that DealerRater may change this Privacy Policy at any time and will post an updated version on the Site highlighting the fact that it has changed and indicating the date of the change. Please revisit this Policy from time to time to ensure that you are comfortable with how DealerRater is handling your Personal Information. 

Opt Out  
You may opt out of receiving communications from DealerRater and our affiliates if you Contact Us and provide your full name and applicable account information, along with your request for opting out. 

Notice to California Residents  
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your Personal Information by DealerRater to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this Privacy Policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to support@dealerrater.com or write us at DealerRater.com, LLC, 203 Crescent Street, Waltham, MA 02453, Attention: Privacy Officer. 

Notice to International Site Visitors  
If you are located outside of the United States, any Personal Information provided to us will be transferred to servers located in the United States and such other countries as designated by DealerRater and will be governed by applicable United States or such other laws and regulations. You consent to such transfer and storage of your Information to the United States and otherwise and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
